Input Text,Anonymized Text,flag,username,timestamp
hello my name is Mr. Frank Pus,<PERSON> my name is <PERSON>,,,2024-04-27 10:50:08.287309
,,,,2024-04-27 10:50:10.570134
"NHS Confidential Clinical Information Summary Patient: JellyKins, Mr Simon Jumbo Date of Birth: 12/12/1956 UBRN: 0004 0123 4567 Age: 25 years NHS: 420 568 7899 Gender: Male UBRN Information Appointment Date/Time: - Referral Created Date: 05-Feb-2021 12:44 Priority: Urgent Clinical Information First 15-Mar-2021 12:44 Submitted: Referred By: JIX, Tricksy (Dr) Clinical Information Last - Referring Organisation: BLOCKSWOOD SURGERY Updated: Address: MIDDLE WAY Named Clinician: - BLOCKS HEATH JUNGLEHAMPTON Allocated Clinician: - DORSET Clinical Context: GI and Liver (Medicine and SO80 10DX Surgery)/Upper GI incl Telephone: 01489 123123 Dyspepsia Location: - Clinical Term: - Patient Information Patient Address: 100 Blankswood Drive Registered Practice: BLOCKSWOOD SURGERY Toffs Heath Address: MIDDLE WAY, TOFFS HEATH Hants, DORSET Telephone (Primary Home): 01489123123 Telephone (Mobile): 07775015050 More contact details available when reviewing online Attachments File Name File 500",<LOCATION> Confidential Clinical Information Summary Patient: <PERSON> Date of Birth: <DATE_TIME> UBRN: <ID> Age: 25 years <LOCATION>: <ID> Gender: Male UBRN Information Appointment Date/Time: - Referral Created Date: <DATE_TIME> 12:44 Priority: Urgent Clinical Information First <DATE_TIME> 12:44 Submitted: Referred By: <PERSON>) Clinical Information Last - Referring Organisation: <LOCATION> Updated: Address: <LOCATION> Named Clinician: - <PERSON> Allocated Clinician: <PERSON> Clinical Context: GI and Liver (Medicine and SO80 10DX Surgery)/Upper GI incl Telephone: <NUMBER> Dyspepsia Location: - Clinical Term: - Patient Information Patient Address: 100 <LOCATION> Drive Registered Practice: <LOCATION> SURGERY <LOCATION> Address: <LOCATION> <PERSON> Telephone (Primary Home): <NUMBER> Telephone (Mobile): <NUMBER> More contact details available when reviewing online Attachments File Name File <NUMBER>,,,2024-04-27 11:15:23.258148
"NHS Confidential Clinical Information Summary Patient: JellyKins, Mr Simon Jumbo Date of Birth: 12/12/1956 UBRN: 0004 0123 4567 Age: 25 years NHS: 420 568 7899 Gender: Male UBRN Information Appointment Date/Time: - Referral Created Date: 05-Feb-2021 12:44 Priority: Urgent Clinical Information First 15-Mar-2021 12:44 Submitted: Referred By: JIX, Tricksy (Dr) Clinical Information Last - Referring Organisation: BLOCKSWOOD SURGERY Updated: Address: MIDDLE WAY Named Clinician: - BLOCKS HEATH JUNGLEHAMPTON Allocated Clinician: - DORSET Clinical Context: GI and Liver (Medicine and SO80 10DX Surgery)/Upper GI incl Telephone: 01489 123123 Dyspepsia Location: - Clinical Term: - Patient Information Patient Address: 100 Blankswood Drive Registered Practice: BLOCKSWOOD SURGERY Toffs Heath Address: MIDDLE WAY, TOFFS HEATH Hants, DORSET Telephone (Primary Home): 01489123123 Telephone (Mobile): 07775015050 More contact details available when reviewing online Attachments File Name File 500",<LOCATION> Confidential Clinical Information Summary Patient: <PERSON> Date of Birth: <DATE_TIME> UBRN: <ID> Age: 25 years <LOCATION>: <ID> Gender: Male UBRN Information Appointment Date/Time: - Referral Created Date: <DATE_TIME> 12:44 Priority: Urgent Clinical Information First <DATE_TIME> 12:44 Submitted: Referred By: <PERSON>) Clinical Information Last - Referring Organisation: <LOCATION> Updated: Address: <LOCATION> Named Clinician: - <PERSON> Allocated Clinician: <PERSON> Clinical Context: GI and Liver (Medicine and SO80 10DX Surgery)/Upper GI incl Telephone: <NUMBER> Dyspepsia Location: - Clinical Term: - Patient Information Patient Address: 100 <LOCATION> Drive Registered Practice: <LOCATION> SURGERY <LOCATION> Address: <LOCATION> <PERSON> Telephone (Primary Home): <NUMBER> Telephone (Mobile): <NUMBER> More contact details available when reviewing online Attachments File Name File <NUMBER>,,,2024-04-27 11:15:25.882813
